var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "وَآتُوا",
        "answer": "and give",
        "pcklId": "526",
        "tlit": "waātū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرًا",
        "answer": "(in) reward",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "ajran",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخَذْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "so We seized him",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "fa-akhadhnāhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاتَّخِذْهُ",
        "answer": "so take Him",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "fa-ittakhidh'hu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذَ",
        "answer": "(let him) take",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "ittakhadha",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْذًا",
        "answer": "(with) a seizure",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "akhdhan",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآخَرُونَ",
        "answer": "and others",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "waākharūna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآخَرُونَ",
        "answer": "and others",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "waākharūna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "446",
        "tlit": "l-arḍu",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the land",
        "pcklId": "447",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "648",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "649",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1393",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمًا",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "alīman",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "2810",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2811",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2812",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2813",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2814",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2815",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2816",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to Him",
        "pcklId": "713",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكُمْ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "714",
        "tlit": "ilaykum",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "715",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "716",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُولِي",
        "answer": "possessors",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "ulī",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَبَتَّلْ",
        "answer": "and devote yourself",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "watabattal",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبْتِيلًا",
        "answer": "(with) devotion",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tabtīlan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْتَغُونَ",
        "answer": "seeking",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "yabtaghūna",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَابَ",
        "answer": "so He has turned",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "fatāba",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَقِيلًا",
        "answer": "heavy",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "thaqīlan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثُلُثَيِ",
        "answer": "two-thirds",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "thuluthayi",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَثُلُثَهُ",
        "answer": "and a third of it",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wathuluthahu",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْجِبَالُ",
        "answer": "and the mountains",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wal-jibālu",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِبَالُ",
        "answer": "the mountains",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "l-jibālu",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَحِيمًا",
        "answer": "and burning fire",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wajaḥīman",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْعَلُ",
        "answer": "(that) will make",
        "pcklId": "322",
        "tlit": "yajʿalu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيلًا",
        "answer": "gracious",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "jamīlan",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسَنًا",
        "answer": "goodly",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "ḥasanan",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُحْصُوهُ",
        "answer": "you count it",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "tuḥ'ṣūhu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٍ",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "khayrin",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرًا",
        "answer": "(will be) better",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "khayran",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "(a little) less",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "adnā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاذْكُرِ",
        "answer": "And remember",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "wa-udh'kuri",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَذْكِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a Reminder",
        "pcklId": "280",
        "tlit": "tadhkiratun",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "912",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّ",
        "answer": "(The) Lord",
        "pcklId": "913",
        "tlit": "rabbu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "914",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "915",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَتِّلِ",
        "answer": "and recite",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "warattili",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْتِيلًا",
        "answer": "(with) measured rhythmic recitation",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tartīlan",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْجُفُ",
        "answer": "will quake",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tarjufu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "331",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "[We] have sent",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We sent",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولًا",
        "answer": "a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "465",
        "tlit": "rasūlan",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولًا",
        "answer": "a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "466",
        "tlit": "rasūlan",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولَ",
        "answer": "the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "467",
        "tlit": "l-rasūla",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّكَاةَ",
        "answer": "the zakah",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "l-zakata",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُزَّمِّلُ",
        "answer": "who wraps himself",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-muzamilu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "زِدْ",
        "answer": "add",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "zid",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبْحًا",
        "answer": "(is) occupation",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "sabḥan",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلًا",
        "answer": "a way",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "sabīlan",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْمَ",
        "answer": "(the) name",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "is'ma",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءُ",
        "answer": "The heaven",
        "pcklId": "343",
        "tlit": "al-samāu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَدُّ",
        "answer": "(is) very hard",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "ashaddu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَشْرِقِ",
        "answer": "(of) the east",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-mashriqi",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاهِدًا",
        "answer": "(as) a witness",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "shāhidan",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "wills",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِيبًا",
        "answer": "gray-haired",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "shīban",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاصْبِرْ",
        "answer": "And be patient",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "wa-iṣ'bir",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَضْرِبُونَ",
        "answer": "traveling",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "yaḍribūna",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَطَعَامًا",
        "answer": "And food",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "waṭaʿāman",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَطَائِفَةٌ",
        "answer": "and (so do) a group",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "waṭāifatun",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَوِيلًا",
        "answer": "prolonged",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ṭawīlan",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَذَابًا",
        "answer": "and a punishment",
        "pcklId": "353",
        "tlit": "waʿadhāban",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَصَىٰ",
        "answer": "But disobeyed",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "faʿaṣā",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَعْظَمَ",
        "answer": "and greater",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wa-aʿẓama",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows",
        "pcklId": "366",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِمَ",
        "answer": "He knows",
        "pcklId": "367",
        "tlit": "ʿalima",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِمَ",
        "answer": "He knows",
        "pcklId": "368",
        "tlit": "ʿalima",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمَغْرِبِ",
        "answer": "and the west",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wal-maghribi",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "غُصَّةٍ",
        "answer": "chokes",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ghuṣṣatin",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْتَغْفِرُوا",
        "answer": "And seek forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "wa-is'taghfirū",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "ghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلِ",
        "answer": "(the) Bounty",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "faḍli",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُنْفَطِرٌ",
        "answer": "(will) break apart",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "munfaṭirun",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَفْعُولًا",
        "answer": "to be fulfilled",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "mafʿūlan",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقَاتِلُونَ",
        "answer": "fighting",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "yuqātilūna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقَدِّرُ",
        "answer": "determines",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "yuqaddiru",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُقَدِّمُوا",
        "answer": "you send forth",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "tuqaddimū",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاقْرَءُوا",
        "answer": "so recite",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "fa-iq'raū",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاقْرَءُوا",
        "answer": "So recite",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "fa-iq'raū",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنَ",
        "answer": "the Quran",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "l-qur'āna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنِ",
        "answer": "the Quran",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "l-qur'āni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقْرِضُوا",
        "answer": "and loan",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wa-aqriḍū",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْضًا",
        "answer": "a loan",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "qarḍan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "a little",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "a little",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "a little",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "1592",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلًا",
        "answer": "(for) Word",
        "pcklId": "1624",
        "tlit": "qīlan",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلًا",
        "answer": "a Word",
        "pcklId": "1712",
        "tlit": "qawlan",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُمِ",
        "answer": "Stand",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "qumi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُومُ",
        "answer": "stand",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "taqūmu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقِيمُوا",
        "answer": "and establish",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "wa-aqīmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقْوَمُ",
        "answer": "and more suitable",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "wa-aqwamu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيبًا",
        "answer": "a heap of sand",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "kathīban",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمُكَذِّبِينَ",
        "answer": "and the deniers",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "wal-mukadhibīna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "281",
        "tlit": "kafartum",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانَتِ",
        "answer": "and will become",
        "pcklId": "1317",
        "tlit": "wakānati",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "1318",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيَكُونُ",
        "answer": "there will be",
        "pcklId": "1319",
        "tlit": "sayakūnu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَيْفَ",
        "answer": "Then how",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "fakayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَنُلْقِي",
        "answer": "will cast",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "sanul'qī",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلَ",
        "answer": "(in) the night",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "al-layla",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "(at) the night",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "(of) the night",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلَ",
        "answer": "the night",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "al-layla",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْضَىٰ",
        "answer": "sick",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "marḍā",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَهِّلْهُمْ",
        "answer": "and allow them respite ",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wamahhil'hum",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَاشِئَةَ",
        "answer": "(the) rising",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "nāshi-ata",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِصْفَهُ",
        "answer": "Half of it",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "niṣ'fahu",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنِصْفَهُ",
        "answer": "and half of it",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "waniṣ'fahu",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّعْمَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the ease",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "l-naʿmati",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَنْفُسِكُمْ",
        "answer": "for yourselves",
        "pcklId": "284",
        "tlit": "li-anfusikum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْقُصْ",
        "answer": "lessen",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "unquṣ",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْكَالًا",
        "answer": "(are) shackles",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ankālan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّهَارِ",
        "answer": "the day",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-nahāri",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّهَارَ",
        "answer": "and the day",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "wal-nahāra",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاهْجُرْهُمْ",
        "answer": "and avoid them",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wa-uh'jur'hum",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَجْرًا",
        "answer": "an avoidance",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "hajran",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَهِيلًا",
        "answer": "pouring down",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "mahīlan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِيلًا",
        "answer": "ruinous",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wabīlan",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجِدُوهُ",
        "answer": "you will find it",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "tajidūhu",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَذَرْنِي",
        "answer": "And leave Me",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "wadharnī",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَطْئًا",
        "answer": "and most potent",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "waṭan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعْدُهُ",
        "answer": "His Promise",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "waʿduhu",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "will you guard yourselves",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "tattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكِيلًا",
        "answer": "(as) Disposer of Affairs",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "wakīlan",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوِلْدَانَ",
        "answer": "the children",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "l-wil'dāna",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَيَسَّرَ",
        "answer": "is easy",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "tayassara",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَيَسَّرَ",
        "answer": "is easy",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "tayassara",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمًا",
        "answer": "a Day",
        "pcklId": "301",
        "tlit": "yawman",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(On the) Day",
        "pcklId": "393",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "73",
        "ayah": "14"
    }
]; 
export default words;